{
    "id": "6dfa0a7c9b13410f890fd16ed182dff7",
    "title": "Had better",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "79485c3c49ba41a59da4bc84421e036b",
            "title": "Had Better",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "You had better ..................... the tickets now.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "buy",
                        "bought",
                        "to buy"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You had better ......................... another car now.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to not buy",
                        "not to buy",
                        "not buy"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "You had better ....................... this medicine.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to take",
                        "take",
                        "taken"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "We had better ..................... on him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "not depend",
                        "not to depend",
                        "to not depend"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You had better ....................... quarrelling with her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to stop",
                        "stop",
                        "stopped"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You had better ..................... the door before you leave.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to lock",
                        "lock",
                        "locked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You had better ...................... in the hostel.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "stay",
                        "to stay",
                        "stayed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I had better ..................... this book soon.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "publish",
                        "to publish",
                        "published"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You had better ....................... him one of these days.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "visit",
                        "to visit",
                        "visited"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You had better ..................... your money in some profitable business.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "invest",
                        "to invest",
                        "invested"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}